## DANIEL WESTBROOK

Front End Web Developer and Designer

Mobile: (+61) 402 697 455 Email: westy12dan@gmail.com Website: westbrookdaniel.com 27 Peasholm Street, City Beach, WA

# **About Me**

I enjoy formulating innovative solutions for Perth businesses and agencies with strategic design thinking. Developing an Designing have been passions of mine for a long time, and I have enjoyed professional experience in both. I always look for new challenges and ways I can develop my knowledge of the latest technologies and methods.

Find out more about me and my projects at westbrookdaniel.com

# **Employment History**

Jun 2020 - Now Front End Developer Unearthed Solutions unearthed.solutions Feb 2019 - Now Website Developer and Graphic Designer Eclipse Design Solutions <u>www.eclipsedesigns.com.au</u> Aug 2019 - Now Web Designer and Developer Contractor

Be Media www.bemedia.com.au

2014 - 2017 Hockey W.A. Coaching

Perth Hockey Stadium, Bentley WA 6102

## **Education**

2018 - 2020 Bachelor of Arts at Curtin University

Digital Design, Creative Advertising and Graphic Design

Dec 2019 - Mar 2020 Digital Marketing Internship at Be Media Perth

1/1122 Hay St, West Perth WA 6005

Nov 2018 Shortlisted for the Charlie Bell Scholarship

for Future Leaders 2019

Apr 2018 - Aug 2018 Web Internship at Be Media Perth

1/1122 Hay St, West Perth WA 6005

Jan 2018 Awarded Curtin Excellence Scholarship 2018

Sacred Heart College, 15 Hocking Parade, Sorrento WA 2001 - 2017

Received ATAR: 91.55

### **Development**

- JS Frameworks (React)
- HTML CSS JavaScript
- CSS Frameworks
- · Wordpress Development
- Version Management (Git, Github)
- Express and Node.js
- · And Lots More

#### **Skills and Abilities**

- Excellent computing and design knowledge
- Great communication and interpersonal skills
- Reliable, punctual and diligent
- Experience working in a team environment and independently
- Excellent attention to detail with strong problem solving ability

#### **Interests**

- · Graphic Design
- · Creative and Visual Arts
- Sport (tennis, hockey)
- · Music and Guitar
- Video Games

### References

Bill Heppard Web Project Manager BirdBrain

3/73 Troy Terrace, Jolimont WA

Daniel Brouse Designer / Director DB Digital Creative Perth WA, Australia Ben Dougherty Principal Technical Lead Unearthed Solutions 191 St Georges Terrace, Perth WA